<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>noisufnoc.com</title><link href="http://noisufnoc.github.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://noisufnoc.github.com/feeds/mike.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://noisufnoc.github.com/</id><updated>2016-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>Pelican Power!</title><link href="http://noisufnoc.github.com/2016/01/22/pelican-power/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Mike</name></author><id>tag:noisufnoc.github.com,2016-01-22:2016/01/22/pelican-power/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pelican power suit" src="http://i.imgur.com/MyYkRgnl.png" title="Pelican Power Suit" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can't guarantee that I'm going to blog all that often, but I've decided to dust this domain off and put out a little bit of content.  I am using &lt;a href="http://blog.getpelican.com/"&gt;Pelican&lt;/a&gt;, which is a &lt;a href="https://www.python.org/"&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; based static blog generator, and since everything is flat files I am able to host it on my &lt;a href="https://github.com/noisufnoc/"&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post, in part is to remind me how to actually publish to GitHub.  I hadn't touched this site in over two years, and couldn't remember the commands I was using to build things so that GitHub pages would serve them up.  After some serious grepping through my bookmarks, I was able to find the original blogger that gave me the info for getting started with Pelican.  &lt;a href="http://blog.aclark.net//2012/09/21/yes-this-blog-is-now-powered-by-pelican/"&gt;Alex Clark's Blog&lt;/a&gt; has some great information for customizing Pelican to run on GitHub pages.  Most importantly, this set of commands to make the blog and commit it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;# make publish; git commit -a -m &amp;quot;Super descriptive commit message&amp;quot;; git push
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Don't forget to add any new files that aren't initially tracked by git.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's all for now, please forgive any misspellings.  Since Pelican uses MarkDown, I'm just writing this entry in vim.  Perhaps I can get the vimspell plugin working...and blog about it later.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="blog"></category><category term="pelican"></category><category term="python"></category></entry></feed>